&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么现在如果我们切换到严格模式，您
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So now if we flip on strict mode, which you
通过将这个严格模式片段放在任何作用域的顶部来完成，最好是在
do by putting this strict mode fragment at the top of any scope, preferably at
程序的顶部，文件的顶部，或任何函数的顶部。
the top of your program, the top of your file, or at the top of any function.
如果打开严格模式，所有相同的处理都将发生。
If you turn on strict mode, all the same processing is going to happen.
所以既然我们已经讲过了，我们就不需要继续强调这一点了。
So since we've run through this, we don't have to keep belaboring this point.
但当我们到达这条线，我们说，嘿，
But when we arrive at this line and we say, hey,
在其他类的范围内，我曾经听说过这个主题的目标引用。
scope of other class, I have this target reference for topic ever heard of it.
没有蓝色大理石，我们去全球范围说，
There's no blue marble, we go to the global scope and we say,
全球范围你听说过主题吗？
global scope have you ever heard of topic, and
全局作用域使用&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：NO进行响应
the global scope kind of respond with &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: No
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：引用错误，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Reference error,
从没听说过。
never heard of it.
这是一种与类型错误不同的错误。
That's a different kind of error than a type error.
类型错误是在找到变量及其值时出现的错误
Type errors are when you found the variable and the value that it is
目前持有是不合法的，无论你想用它做什么。
currently holding is not legal to do whatever you're trying to do with it.
例如执行函数，访问未定义NULL上的属性，
Like execute a function, access a property on an undefined null,
诸如此类的事情，那是类型错误。
things like that, that's type error.
引用错误是，我找不到那个变量，
A reference error is, I couldn't find that variable,
我不能给你一个变量来使用，好吗？
I can't give you a variable to use, okay?
这就是我们希望一直发生的事情。
That's what we would like to happen all of the time.
现在它是严格模式的结果，您会得到一个引用错误。
It now happens as the result of strict mode, you get a reference error.
抱歉，没有大理石，运气不好。
Sorry, no marble, tough luck.
所以很多理由中的一个就是为什么它会对
So one of the many, many reasons why it would be good for
您使用的是严格模式。
you to be using strict mode.
它会避免这样的错误，因为几乎可以肯定这是一个错误，
It will avoid mistakes like this, cuz it almost certainly a mistake,
它不应该是你有意创建的全球性的东西，对吗？
it should not be something you intentionally try to create global, yes?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：严格模式在ES6上总是漂亮吗
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Is strict mode always pretty on ES6
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：严格模式不是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Strict mode is not
一直开着。
always on.
像气泡和气泡这样的工具是真的
It's true that tools like Bubble and
其他传送器基本上总是把严格的模式放在那里。
other transpilers basically always put the strict mode in there for you.
所以如果你用的是泄露的代码
So if you're using transpired code,
几乎可以肯定，您的代码正在严格模式下运行。
it was almost a virtual certainty that your code is running in strict mode.
但JavaScript不是默认的严格模式，因为那样会打破一大堆
But JavaScript is not default the strict mode because then that would break a bunch
程序。
of programs.
所以这是20年前写的什么的。
So that were written 20 years ago or something.
因此，由于向后兼容，您将始终必须选择严格模式。
So because of backwards compatible, you will always have to opt into strict mode.
ES6和ES6中某些机制内部的另一个小警告
Another little caveat inside of certain kinds of mechanisms within ES6 and
展望未来，假设它处于严格模式。
going forward, it is assumed to be in strict mode.
所以你甚至不输入它，所以在课堂上稍后讨论，
So you don't even type it, so inside of a class to talk about later in the course,
或者在ES6模块内部，我们将在本单元的后面讨论。
or inside of ES6 module, which we'll talk about later in this unit.
在这两种模式中，假设是严格模式，您甚至不需要将
Inside of both of those, strict mode is assumed, you don't even have to put
严格模式，只是假设代码在严格模式下运行。
the strict mode, is just assume that, that code is running in strict mode.
但作为一般规则
But as a general rule for
JavaScript本身，除非您选择加入，否则它不是严格模式。
JavaScript itself, it's not in strict mode unless you opt-in.
关于严格模式，您应该了解的是，
What you should know about strict mode is,
它本质上是语言的未来，更多和
it's essentially the future of the language, more and
更多的类和模块将采用严格模式。
more will be like classes and modules and assume the strict mode.
所以你还是去咬子弹吧。
So you might as well just go ahead and bite that bullet.
它已经存在了将近十年，基本上是十年。
It's been around now for almost a decade basically a decade.
所以如果你不使用严格模式的话肯定是时候了，
So it's definitely time if you're not using strict mode,
继续承受痛苦和转换，好吗？
go ahead and take the pain and switch, yes?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：如果你不使用严格的，有没有新的功能不起作用？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: If you don't use strict are there newer features that won't work?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：他们有时确实会谈论或讨论，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: They do sometimes talk about or discuss,
此功能仅在严格模式或非严格模式下以特定方式工作。
this feature will only work a certain way in strict mode or not-strict mode.
因为如果他们增加了一个新功能，
Because if they add a new feature,
他们没有任何机会破解20年前的某个人的代码。
they don't have any chances of having broken somebody's code from 20 years ago.
我不知道有什么具体的例子
I'm not aware of any specific examples where this
如果您没有切换到严格模式，语法甚至不可用。
syntax is not even available, if you haven't switched on strict mode.
但这肯定是在可能的范围内，这样的事情可能
But it is certainly within the realm of possibility that things like that may
否则行为会有所不同。
occur, or that behaviors will be different.
可以有细微差别的不同行为，就像我们在这里看到的。
There can be nuanced different behaviors, like we're seeing here.
一种可能是宽容的，另一种可能不是。
One might be permissive and one might be not.
严格模式的另一个示例具有差异和
Another example of strict mode having a difference and
它与ES6无关。
it has nothing to do with ES6.
回到ES5，当引入严格模式时，
Back in ES5, when strict mode was introduced,
我们有几种不同的错误，如果你不在
we had several different kinds of errors that if you were not in
严格模式他们是错误的，但他们是沉默的，他们只是什么都没发生。
strict mode they were errors, but they were silent, they just nothing happened.
例如，尝试分配给只读属性，或者
So for example, trying to assign to a read only property, or
一个只读变量，它只是默默地不做任何事情。
a read only variable, it just would silently not do anything.
它不会真的完成任务。
It wouldn't actually do the assignment.
一旦你打开严格模式，现在你开始得到这些错误。
Once you turn on strict mode, now you start getting errors for those.
因此，可观察到的行为会因此而有所不同，但是
So there are differences in observable behavior as a result of that, but
我不一定要说有很多表面上的特性是你不能做到的
I wouldn't necessarily say that there's a lot of ostensible features that you can't
在没有它们的情况下使用&gt；&gt；扬声器1：问题，所以
use without them &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Question, so
主题，在严格模式下，它们总是必须被定义，对吧，差不多？
the topic, in strict mode, they always have to be defined, right, pretty much?
我的问题是，如果主题在全局范围内，它仍然是相同的错误，对吗？
My question is if topic was in a global scope, it's still the same error, right?
凯尔·辛普森：我不知道。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I don't know.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：如果-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果线路7在
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: If the- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If line 7 was in
全球范围？
the global scope?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：没错。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Exactly. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：它还会爆炸吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: It would still blow up?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它仍然会爆炸。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It still blows up.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：好的，就这样。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Okay, that's all.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：您不能自动创建变量，必须声明它们。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You cannot auto create variables, you have to declare them.